(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
王国内で繰り広げられる音楽祭。
A music festival held within the kingdom.
この日を待ってたと言わんばかりに国民たちは
The citizens, as if they had been waiting for this day,
各々で応援するための道具を用意し、
each prepared their own tools to cheer,
そして、広場へと向かいました。
and then, they headed to the town square.
Say! ファンファーレ!
Say! Fanfare!
ほっと一息お茶ですぞ
Take a breather with some tea
はいどうぞ
Here you go
いつもの場所から元気よくせーのでご挨拶
From the usual place, let's greet everyone with energy
おはこん狐
Ohakonkitsune
始めましょう。
Let's begin.
おしゃべりをしてもっと過ごす
Spend more time chatting
そんな毎日愛おしくて。
I cherish those everyday moments.
あれもこれも手を出したくなりがちです。
I tend to want to try a bit of everything.
歌とかステージはまだまだ恥ずかしいけど
Singing and the stage are still embarrassing to me,
支え合ってほら届けますよ、この声を。
but with our mutual support, look, I'll deliver this voice.
Say! ほらその顔を上げて
Say! Look, lift up your face,
みんなで手を取れば
and if we all take each other's hands.
High!
まだまだ道の途中
We're still in the middle of our journey,
世界を越えよう。
let's cross over the world.
Say! ほら推し事も
Say! Look, supporting my favorite also
止まらない、全力ですから。
won't stop, because I'm giving it my all.
夢を書き換えたら
Once we rewrite our dreams,
追いかけ続けよう。
let's keep chasing them.
共に繋ぐファンファーレ。
A fanfare that connects us together.
ちょっとやらかした時でも
Even when I mess up a little,
もう大丈夫！
it's okay now!
気持ち切り換えて
I'll switch my mindset
ほっとしちゃう広場には
and in the square where I can relax,
集合ですよ！
everyone gather!
背伸びをして
I'll stretch myself
お腹減ったらすぐモグモグと
and if I get hungry, I'll start munching right away.
お茶の間いますか？なやつで
With the kind of greeting like 'Is anyone in the living room?'
黒いあの子には内緒にしてほしいです。
I want to keep it a secret from that black one.
仲間の力とお友達の皆さんとも
With the power of my comrades and all my friends,
叶えたい思いは言葉にして
I'll put my feelings I want to fulfill into words,
一つずつ。
one by one.
Say! ほらその手を上げて
Say! Look, raise those hands,
みんなで輪になれば
and if we all form a circle.
High!
まだまだ成長途中
We're still in the middle of growing,
問題ないでしょ。
there's no problem, right?
Say! ほら明るく元気な
Say! Look, a bright and energetic
心が第一ですから
heart is the top priority.
いつも 輝き続けよう
Let's always keep on shining
共に繋ぐ アンコール
An encore we connect together
何もかもが新しくて 右も左も分からない
Everything is so new, and I don't know my left from right
時も頑張れたのは 一人じゃないから
But the reason I could keep trying was because I wasn't alone
一つ一つ お願いが 後押しになって一歩ずつでも
Each and every wish became a support, and even if just step by step
私は自分らしく磨いていく フューチャー
I'll keep polishing my future in my own way
理想もイメージもまだまだ 手探りしても
Even if my ideals and images are still a work in progress
響き合ってほら 世界は今 彩って
Look, they're resonating, and the world is now taking on color
Say! さあ その顔上げて みんなで手を取れば
Say! Now, lift up your face, and if we all take each other's hands
Nice! これから夢の先へ 駆け出そう
Nice! Let's run towards the future of our dreams together
Say! ほら 押しも押されぬ 止まらない全力ですから
Say! Look, we're unstoppable, moving forward with all our might
大好きな想いが 溢れそうなほど
With feelings of love almost overflowing
共に繋ぐ ファンファーレ
The fanfare we connect together
Woah-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh...
SUPERNOVA
作詞・作曲・編曲：小池竜暉
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Ryuki Koike
甘く ほろ苦い夢
A sweet, bittersweet dream
これでいいか これがいいか 追いかけたあの日
Is this okay? Is this what's best? Those days I spent chasing after it
ここに 間違いはなくて 正解もなくて
There's no mistake here, and there's no correct answer either
自分次第で 怖くて仕方ないけど
It's all up to me, and I can't help being scared, but
誰かじゃない 君と見たい 景色は鮮明で
It's not just anyone, the scenery I want to see with you is so vivid
それじゃ ここで 足踏みなんか していられないじゃん
Well then, I can't just be standing still here, can I?
Oh yes! 無数の星の中
Oh yes! Among the countless stars
Oh yes! 光は君がくれた
Oh yes! You were the one who gave me light
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! もっと 超えていけるさ
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! We can go even further
Oh yes! SUPERNOVA 起きろ今
Oh yes! SUPERNOVA, wake up now
Oh yes! 何度だって飛べる
Oh yes! I can fly as many times as it takes
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! これは紛れもなく僕らの奇跡 High Five!
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! This is undoubtedly our miracle, High Five!
Woah-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh...
これから 泣きじゃくる日でも
Even on days when I'm crying my eyes out from now on
いつだって ここにおいで 強がりはいらないよ
Come here anytime, you don't need to put on a brave face
一人じゃない 君もほら 僕ら手を取り合って
You're not alone, see? Let's take each other's hands
笑おう 叫ぼう あの空の向こうへ
Let's laugh, let's shout, towards the other side of that sky
Oh yes! 無数の星の中
Oh yes! Among the countless stars
Oh yes! 交わした約束も
Oh yes! Even the promises we made
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! きっと 叶えられるさ
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! I'm sure we can make them come true
Oh yes! SUPERNOVA 駆けろ今
Oh yes! SUPERNOVA, run now
Oh yes! 誰一人欠かせない
Oh yes! Not a single person is expendable
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! あの日描いた夢の先まで High Five!
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! To the future of the dreams we drew that day, High Five!
この今を 愛せるように
So that I can love this 'now'
君に向けて歌うよ 心が叫んで
I'll sing to you, my heart is shouting
Oh yes! 無数の星の中
Oh yes! Among the countless stars
Oh yes! 光は君がくれた
Oh yes! You were the one who gave me light
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! もっと 超えていけるさ
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! We can go even further
Oh yes! SUPERNOVA 起きろ今
Oh yes! SUPERNOVA, wake up now
Oh yes! 何度だって飛べる
Oh yes! I can fly as many times as it takes
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! これは紛れもなく僕らの奇跡
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! This is undoubtedly our miracle
いつまでも ありのまま 君が君らしくあれるように
Always, just as you are, so that you can be yourself
もっと ずっと 届けよう 不思議と怖くはないんだ 綺麗な空 どこまでも
I'll keep reaching out, more and more, strangely I'm not afraid, to the beautiful sky, everywhere
怖くはないさ 行こう
It's not scary, let's go.
この物語は終わらない
This story will never end.
Woah-oh, woah-oh-oh-oh...
Woah-oh, woah-oh-oh-oh, woah-oh...
はーい！
Haaai!
ということで、しょっぱなから2曲
歌わせていただきました。
And with that, I've just sung two songs
right from the start.
皆さんこんばんきーつねー！
Good evening, everyone-kon!
フブキングダムの国王、白上フブキです！
I'm the King of Fubuki Kingdom, Shirakami Fubuki!
イエーイ！
Yay!
見てるー？
Are you watching?
はい。ちょっとね、もう暑いや。ふふっ。
Whew. Man, I'm already hot. Hehe.
本日はですね、フブキングダムの機密解禁ということで、
皆さんね、ソワソワしてるんじゃないかと思います。
Today is the day we lift the secrecy of Fubuki Kingdom,
so I'm sure you're all feeling a bit restless.
ハッシュタグはこちら！
Here's the hashtag!
機密…機密…機密解禁って何だ。やばい、舌が回らなくなっちゃった。
Secret... Secret... What's with "Secret Info Unveiled"? Oh no, I'm tongue-tied.
機密解禁フブキングダムです。
#機密解禁フブキングダム (Secret Info Unveiled Fubuki Kingdom).
なんかすごいソシャゲのタイトルみたいでかっこいいなと思って付けました。
イエーイ、よろしくお願いします。
I chose it because it sounded cool, like the title of a social game.
Yay, please support me today.
さて、ちょっとね、まず一つ目の重大ではないんですけどプチ告知が、
プチ告知というかプチお披露目がございまーす。
Now, it's not exactly a major one,
but I have a small announcement—or rather, a small reveal.
さて、どこにいるかな？
あ、いたいたいた。おいでー！
Now, where is it?
Ah, there they are. Come on out!
わー、すこんぶー！
Woah, Sukonbu!
なんと、なんと、お前らみんな国民が、
Believe it or not, every one of you citizens...
こんなにかわちいお体を手に入れたぞー！えっ。
...has obtained such a cute body! Eh.
みんな可愛い、可愛い。よかったね、みんな。
Everyone is so cute, so cute. I'm glad for you all.
みんなもついに、こうやって白上の隣に立つ時が来たんだ。
わー、可愛い。
The time has finally come for you all to stand by my side like this.
Woah, cute.
嬉しいね。嬉しいの。
It makes me happy. You're happy too?
はい、よかったー。
Yes, wonderful.
実はですね、これはね、スカーフはJPすこんぶなんだけど、
Actually, this scarf belongs to the JP Sukonbu, but...
実は裏にですね、あの海外のすこんぶフレンズも実はいるというね。
...on the back, there are actually the overseas Sukonbu Friends too.
今回はちょっと代表として、JPすこんぶのいつものスカーフの
すこんぶにお越しいただきました。
Today, as a representative, we have the JP Sukonbu
with the usual scarf here.
で、さらに、さらに、後ろをご覧ください。
ふぶらー！
And furthermore, look behind me.
Hubura!
「GO」言うておる。
He's saying "GO."
お前デカすぎんだろ。
You're way too big.
そう、ふぶらもですね、この機密解禁に駆けつけてくれました。
ヤッホー。
That's right, Hubura also rushed here for this unveiling.
Yoo-hoo.
拳見えん。建物の間から見える。ふふっ。
I can't see the fist. I can see it between the buildings. Hehe.
可愛いー。ねー。
So cute. Right?
ということで、今日は一緒に重大発表していきましょう。
So, let's make the big announcements together today.
さてさて、じゃあね、早速もうやっちゃいましょうかね。
Now then, shall we get right into it?
告知いっぱいありますので、ちょっと一番すごいのからいっちゃおうかなー。
There are lots of announcements, so I think I'll start with the biggest one.
ピーピー！ピーピー！
Pee-pee! Pee-pee!
ちょちょちょちょ、え？何何？ピーピー？
Wait, wait, wait, eh? What, what? Pee-pee?
全くフブさんたら。
Oh, Fubu-san, really.
え、何？
Eh, what?
フブさん、うるさいよ。
Fubu-san, you're being noisy.
え、そっち？
Eh, you're the ones?
全く困ったさんなんだから。
You're such a handful.
何がだよ！
What are you talking about!
何をシレッと重大告知しようとしてるんですか。
Why are you trying to make big announcements so casually?
だって重大告知する配信だから。
Because this stream is for making big announcements.
いやいや、そんなの引っ張るに決まってるじゃない、最後まで！
No, no, you're supposed to drag it out until the very end!
当たり前だよ、引っ張らせますよ、のびのびだよ、のびのび！
Of course, we're going to make you drag it out. Streeeetch it out!
え、てかどうした二人とも。ハロウィンはもう終わったんだよ。
Anyway, what's with you two? Halloween is already over.
終わってない！
It's not over!
トリックオアトリート、トリート。
Trick or treat, treat.
お菓子もねえ、飯もねえ、ミコメットミコメット！
No candy, no food, Micomet Micomet!
うちらも何もないよ。ミコメットミコメット！
We have nothing either. Micomet Micomet!
可愛い、ミコメット。ビビデバビデブーだ。
So cute, Micomet. Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo!
やめて、何、ビビデブー。
Stop it, what's with "Bibbidi-Boo"?
わー！ミコメット配信！
Whoa! A Micomet stream!
何しに来たの本当に。邪魔しに来ただけ？
Why are you really here? Just to interfere?
ま、何で来たのかといいますと、
Well, as for why we're here...
せーの、重大告知をさせないために、邪魔をしに来ましたー！
One, two... We're here to interfere so you can't make the big announcements!
これから魔法をかけるので、覚悟してください。
We're going to cast a spell now, so be prepared.
魔法？魔法使えるの？
Magic? You can use magic?
そうです！
That's right!
当たり前です！
Of course!
決まってます！
Obviously!
怖いんだけど。白上、そんなことできないよ。
You're scaring me. I can't do anything about that.
今うちらだけこの杖持ってるから。見てこの杖。
Only we have these wands right now. Look at them.
確かに、何その杖。すご。
True, what are those wands? Amazing.
可愛いでしょ、これ。
Cute, aren't they?
すごいでしょ。ミコメットすごいでしょ。
Great, right? Micomet is great, right?
ま、魔法をかけて邪魔をしてしまうという役割なんですね、我々は。
Well, our role is to cast spells and get in your way.
やめろー！やめろー！人の告知で好き勝手すんの。
Stop it! Stop it! Don't just do whatever you want with my announcements.
ぷえちゃんうるさいよ。全くぷえちゃん可愛いな。
Pue-chan, you're noisy. Pue-chan is just so cute though.
すこんぶ、すこんぶだよ。お前すこんぶいじめて。
Sukonbu, it's a Sukonbu. You're bullying the Sukonbu.
こら、こら、小さい可愛いものいじめるな。
Hey, hey, don't bully small, cute things.
やめてやめて、可愛い。
Stop it, stop it, it's cute.
小さい可愛いものは、いじめたくなるんだよ。
怒ってる怒ってる。
You just want to tease small, cute things.
It's angry, it's angry.
今ぷんぷんしてたよ。ほら、ほら。
It was just pouting. Look, look.
可愛い、立ち向かうのはまずい。ミコ見ろみんなで。可愛いね。
Cute, it's bad to stand up to it. Everyone look at Miko. How cute.
あー、ということでね。
So, anyway...
まあ、皆さんちょっとね、こちらに。フブさんはこちらに。
Well, everyone, please come over here. Fubu-san, you go there.
さあ、こちらにこちらに。ほらほら。
Come here, come here. Come on.
ハの字にね、ちゃんとして。
Line up properly in a V-shape.
何？ 何が始まるんです？
What? What's starting?
動くなよ。絶対に動いたらちょっと色々やばいことになっちゃうから。
Don't move. If you move, things will get really bad.
うち等もうちょっと後ろだよ。
We should be a bit further back.
何？ 何がお、始まるんです？
What? What's... starting?
それじゃあ、やってみましょうよ！
Well then, let's do it!
はい！
Yes!
せーの！
One, two...
ビビディ・バビディ・ブー！
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo!
何？ え？ 何か来た！
What? Eh? Something's coming!
はあ、力を使ったぜ。
Phew, that took a lot of power.
いや、かなりのマナを消費したね。
Yeah, it consumed quite a bit of mana.
お？ 白上？ あれ？ お？ あれ？
Oh? Shirakami? Huh? Oh? Wait?
わー！ すこん部になってるー！
Whoa! I've turned into a Sukonbu!
え、フブさん！ フブさん！
Eh, Fubu-san! Fubu-san!
違う、そっちは、フブさん、踊れ！
No, over there, Fubu-san, dance!
何、踊る？
What, dance?
結構セクシーな感じで。
In a pretty sexy way.
やめろよー！
Stop it!
うまい！ うますぎる！
Great! You're too good!
セクシーな踊り踊ってないから！
I'm not doing a sexy dance!
セクシーだー！ これなんだ、このちんちくりんは？
So sexy! What's this, this tiny thing?
なんだこれ！ めっちゃちんちくりん、これなんだ？
What is this! So tiny. What is this?
フブさんはこんなにちっちゃかったんだね。
Fubu-san was this small, huh?
ちっちゃくねーよ！
I'm not small!
ちっちゃかったんだね。
You were small.
可愛いー、横幅がすごい。
So cute. She's so wide.
なんだ、なんだこれ、魔封じ？
What, what is this, a magic seal?
あ、ということでね。
Ah, and so...
まあ、元に戻りたかったら、みこたちとゲームをして、この魔法を解きなすわーい！
Well, if you want to go back to normal, play a game with us and break this spell!
解きなすわーい！
Break the spell!
それではいきますよ。題して...
Here we go. Entitled...
フブ抜き対決ー！
Fubu-nuki Showdown!
フブ抜き対決
Fubu-nuki Showdown
何かカード来た。
Some cards appeared.
カードがいっぱい出てきた。
Lots of cards appeared.
ということで、説明をお願いします。
And now, please explain the rules.
ルールの説明参ります。
I'll proceed with the rule explanation.
はい。目の前に、星のペア、ハートのペア...
Yes. Before you, a pair of stars, a pair of hearts...
ジョーカー、フブキングの絵柄、合わせて６枚のカードがありますよね、皆さん。
A Joker, and a Fubuking design. Total of 6 cards, right everyone?
見えます、見えます。こちらに。
We see them. Over here.
お互いのカードを引き合ってペアの図柄をゲットしたら捨てる。最後の１枚「フブキングカード」→勝利！「ジョーカー」→負け
Draw cards from each other and discard if you get a matching pair. If your last card is the 'Fubuking Card' -> Win! 'Joker' -> Lose.
こちらですよ。はい。
Here they are. Yes.
これらのカードを３枚ずつ対戦する二人に配ります。
These cards will be dealt, 3 each, to the two players.
この二人にはこれらのカードを引き合うゲームをしてもらいます。
The two will play a game of drawing these cards from each other.
はい。ペアの絵柄を揃えたら捨てていき...
Yes. If you get a matching pair, discard them...
最後の１枚としてフブキングカードを持っていることができれば勝利。
...and if your last card is the Fubuking card, you win.
ジョーカーを持っていたら負けとなります。
If you hold the Joker, you lose.
えー、やだー、負けたくない！
Ehh, no way, I don't want to lose!
ただし、トランプのババ抜きと違って、手札の絵柄が揃った場合は...
However, unlike regular Old Maid, if your hand matches...
立て続けにカードを引くことができます。
You can draw cards in succession.
手札の図柄が揃った人が更に次のカードを引く。手持ちのカードが無くても最後まで引いて勝負を決める
The person whose hand matches gets to draw the next card. Even if you run out of cards, you keep drawing until the end to decide the winner.
もし手持ちのカードがなくなったとしても、最後まで引いて勝負を決めることになります。
Even if you run out of cards, you draw until the end to determine the winner.
ああ、なるほどね。
Ah, I see.
まあ何言ってるか分かんないと思うけど、みこも分かんない。
Well, you probably don't get what I'm saying, but Miko also doesn't know.
まあやってみないと分かんないわけ。やってみないといけませんわね。
Well, you won't know until you try. We have to try it.
え、でも何か、これ手札３枚しかないってことだよね。
Eh, but wait, this means we only have 3 cards in hand.
そうよ、だから注意しないとすぐに負けちゃう。そんな時のために、私用意しました。
That's right, so if you're not careful, you'll lose instantly. For such a time, I've prepared something.
シャッフルチャンス！
Shuffle Chance!
何？ シャッフルチャンス？
What? Shuffle Chance?
シャッフルチャンスとは、このままだと自分が負けてしまうと思った時に...
Shuffle Chance is, when you think you're about to lose as things are...
「シャッフルチャンス！」 自分がピンチ→相手の手札を入れ替えることができる。残り手札１枚ずつの時は使えない
'Shuffle Chance!' When in a pinch -> You can swap hands with your opponent. Cannot be used when both have 1 card left.
相手の手札とまるまる入れ替えることができる機能です。
...a feature that allows you to swap hands entirely with your opponent.
もし使いたい時には、ゲーム中に『シャッフルチャンス！』と叫んでくれれば...
If you want to use it, just shout 'Shuffle Chance!' during the game...
私がぶぶぶぶぶーってやるのでね。
...and I'll go 'vroom vroom vroom'.
ほうほう、なるほどね、シャッフルチャンス。分かった、シャッフルチャンス。
Ho ho, I see, Shuffle Chance. Got it, Shuffle Chance.
うちはそっちすこん部だからな。フブさんもね、ちゃんと覚えてね。
We're on that Sukonbu's side. Fubu-san, remember it well, okay?
そっちすこん部なんだね。あ、こっちだったね。
So you're on the Sukonbu side. Ah, it was this side.
ただし、残りの手札が１枚の時にシャッフルチャンスは使えないものとします。
However, Shuffle Chance cannot be used when you have only one card left.
２枚ないとダメなんだ。
So you need 2 cards.
そうですね、じゃないとちょっとね、ヌルゲーになっちゃうんで。
Yes, otherwise it becomes too easy.
このシャッフルチャンスは、ゲームを始める前にじゃんけんをして、勝った方に与えられます。
This Shuffle Chance is given to the winner of a rock-paper-scissors match before the game starts.
逆に負けた方は、先にカードを引く権利を与えられますというルールになっております。
Conversely, the loser is given the right to draw first. That's the rule.
なるほどね。はいはい。まあ簡単なババ抜きと神経衰弱がなんかこう混ざったようなやつね。
I see. Okay. So it's like a simple mix of Old Maid and Concentration.
なるほどね。混ざったようなやつね。
I see. A mix-like thing.
ほうほうほう、じゃあちょっとやっていきますか。
Ho ho ho, well then, shall we give it a try?
そうですね。これもね、ちょっとシャッフルチャンス忘れないようにしなきゃいけないね。
Indeed. And we must be careful not to forget the Shuffle Chance.
絶対に忘れないでくださいね。大事な、大事なじゃんけんなんで。さあ、さあ、さあ。
Please definitely don't forget it. It's an important, important rock-paper-scissors match. Come on.
ということで、あの、すこん部のフブキ、フブキのすこん部。
So, anyway, Sukonbu Fubuki, Fubuki's Sukonbu.
いや、こっち、白上。そっちでもいいんですけど。
No, it's Shirakami over here. But that's fine too.
つまり、このメンバーで勝負ということで。
In short, a battle with this group.
えー！ じゃあちょっとね、フブさん、というかスコンプ、こっちに来なさい。
Ehh! Well then, Fubu-san, or rather Sukonbu, come over here.
え、あ、こっちに来なさい。フブさんはこっち、フブさんはこっち。
Eh, ah, come here. Fubu-san, over here. Fubu-san, over here.
え、みこさんとチーム組むってこと？
Eh, you mean I'm teaming up with Miko-san?
いや、それではない。
No, that's not it.
違うんかい！ そうではないんかい。
You're not?! That's not it.
ということで、じゃあまず１回目は...
And so, for the first round...
すこん部（白上フブキ）vs すいちゃん！
Sukonbu (Shirakami Fubuki) vs Sui-chan!
あ、はい。フブさんvsすいちゃん。
Ah, yes. Fubu-san vs Sui-chan.
こんにちは、すこん部さん。
Hello, Sukonbu-san.
白上だよ。
I'm Shirakami.
あ、フブキさん。
Oh, Fubuki-san.
紛らわしい。
Confusing.
じゃあまず、真剣勝負ということで、じゃんけんからやっていきますか。
Well then, for a serious battle, let's start with rock-paper-scissors.
じゃんけん。準備いいですか？
Rock-paper-scissors. Are you ready?
最初はグー、じゃんけんぽい！
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
チョキ！
Scissors!
パーだろそれ。
That's paper.
チョキだよ。チョキだよ。
It's scissors. It's scissors.
本当にチョキしてる…
You're really doing scissors...
チョキしてるっていうことにするわ。
Let's just say it's scissors.
あいこでしょい！
Rock-paper-scissors!
パー！
Paper!
本当にパー？
Really paper?
パーだ。パー。
It was paper. Paper.
勝った。
I won.
負けました。
I lost.
ということで勝者、ホ部。じゃあ、
ミコさんの勝ちということで。
And so, the winner is Ho-bu. Well,
so Miko-san wins.
じゃあ白上がシャッフルチャンスできるんだ。
Then I, Shirakami, get to do a shuffle chance.
そうだね。すいちゃんが
シャッフルチャンスをゲットしました。
Right. Suichan got the shuffle chance.
あ、おめでとう。じゃあすいちゃん先行ね。
Ah, congrats. Then Suichan goes first.
はい。よし、頑張るぞ。
Yes. Alright, let's do this.
いけるぞ！
You can do it!
じゃあ、準備いいですか？
Now, are you ready?
はい。はい。じゃあ皆さんの…
こちらのカードをシャッフルしまして…
Yes. Okay. Now, everyone's...
Let's shuffle these cards...
あ、ちょっとカードチェックしますか。
Ah, let's check the cards first.
じゃあまず、ミコさん。
はいはいはい。意気込みどうですか？
Now, first, Miko-san.
Yes, yes. How's your motivation?
いや、まあちょっとね、最近運がいいような悪いような…
だけど、ここいらで運を取り戻そうと思いますよ。
Well, lately my luck's been good and bad...
But I'm going to take my luck back right here.
フブキなくないよ、そんな格好で言われても。
It's not very Fubuki-like, hearing that from you in that outfit.
うっせぇ！
Shut up!
パンツ見るぞ！
I'm gonna look at your panties!
やめてよ！
Stop it!
じゃあすいちゃんの意気込みどうですか？
Then, Suichan, how's your motivation?
全く、運と言えば私。私と言えば運。
Seriously, luck means me. And I mean luck.
分かってますよね？だから私は今日ここで勝って…
You understand, right? That's why I will win here today and...
フブキ、お前に重大告知をさせない！
Fubuki, I won't let you make the major announcement!
最低だよ！マジで最低だよ！
You're the worst! Truly the worst!
勝つしかねえ！ということで先行のすいちゃん、
まず一枚選んでください。
I have to win! So Suichan, going first,
please pick one card.
勝負開始！
Let the match begin!
フブさん、どれ引いたらいいと思う？
Fubusan, which one should I pull?
一番右、おすすめ。
The far right one, I recommend it.
お、おすすめから始まりましたよ、心理戦。心理戦が始まりましたよ。
Oh, the recommendation started it, the psychological warfare.
右かな？左は止めたほうがいい、左は止めたほうがいいよ。
Is it the right? You'd better avoid the left.
そういう時は「ダメ」って言われたもんだろう、これ！
In times like this, you pick the one they said 'no' to, this one!
本当にそれ？大丈夫？
Really that one? Are you sure?
わわわわわ、魔法の力で！本当にこれだ！
Wa wa wa, with the power of magic! This is truly it!
どうだ！
How's that!
それでは、どうですか？揃ったものが…
Now then, how is it? Did they match...
あったー！よっしゃー！やったー！
There it is! Alright! Yay!
イエーイ。星が揃いました。
Yay. The stars matched.
まあまあまだこれからですからね。
最後に残ってるか残ってないかな、悪いカードがね。
Well well, it's just beginning.
Whether the bad card remains or not, we'll see.
あー、まだ引けるんだよね、これは。
Ah, I can still pull, right?
あ、もうシャッフル、もうシャッフルするんですか？
Ah, another shuffle, are we shuffling already?
早すぎるだろ！
That's too fast!
おー、混ぜ混ぜ混ぜ…
Oh, mixing, mixing...
待てよ！私のカード！
Wait! My cards!
混ぜ混ぜ混ぜ混ぜ…よし。
Mixing, mixing... alright.
なるほどね。ふぅ、どうなったかな。
I see. Phew, I wonder how it turned out.
おい、これ好み見てみよう。
Hey, let's look at the preference.
おい、これまずいやんけ。
Hey, this is bad.
待って、ってことは私これ、
揃ってしまったらいけない、これはどうなるの。
Wait, so that means if I... match these, it'll be bad.
シャッフルチャンスしたら白上はターンを消費したということなんですかね？
Does doing a shuffle chance mean Shirakami consumes her turn?
まあまあ、すいちゃんの引けるのかな？
すいちゃんの引いてください、そこは。はい。
Well well, can Suichan pull it?
Suichan, please pull there. Yes.
これは私が今ジョーカーを持たされたので、
Since I was just given the Joker,
この状態で私が絵柄揃えてしまうと、
私がジョーカーを持った状態になってしまうので、
if I match the patterns in this state,
I'll be left holding the Joker,
フブキングダムを引かないといけないんですよ。
so I have to pull the Fubuki Kingdom card.
ほう、賢いじゃん。
Oh, that's smart.
賢いじゃないですか。
Aren't you smart?
え、わかんないけど、どっち？
どっちだったっけかな？あー、こっちだわ。
Eh, I don't know, which one?
Which one was it? Ah, it's this one.
心理をカイジで見てやろう、な、目、目、目やで。
I'll see through your psychology like in Kaiji, your eyes, eyes, eyes.
嘘ついてる時の目の動きをしっかり見ててください。
Watch the eye movement when someone is lying.
何も見せない！何も見せないんだから！
I'm not showing anything! I won't show anything!
こういう時は「こっち」って言われたほうだよ。これ。
In times like this, you pick the one they said is 'this way'. This one.
本当にそれ？
Really that one?
うーーー、魔法の力で！魔法の手品だ！
Uooooh, with the power of magic! It's a magic trick!
さあ、揃ったものがありますか？
Now, do you have a match?
どうぞ。ババーーン！あったー！よっしゃー！
Here. Ta-da! Got it! Alright!
待って、待って、これ今からシャッフルするから。
Wait, wait, I'm going to shuffle now.
シャッフル。シャッフルシャッフル…
シャッフル見ないよね、フブさん？
Shuffle. Shuffle, shuffle...
You're not looking at the shuffle, Fubusan?
見ないよ、見ないよ、可愛いね、可愛いね…
I'm not looking, I'm not looking, cute, cute...
こうして、こうして、愛して、こうして…魔法を使って！
Like this, like this, love this, like this... using magic!
はい、じゃあ引いてください。いいですよ。
Okay, now please pull. Go ahead.
どれだ…えー、ちょっとすいちゃんどれ、教えて。
Which one is it... eh, Suichan, tell me which one.
すこん部、すこん部という名のフブキに入ってるすこん部、教えてくれよ。
Sukonbu, the Sukonbu that are part of Fubuki called Sukonbu, tell me.
そうだよ、お前は仲間だ。どれがいいと思う？
That's right, you are an ally. Which one do you think is good?
わかんねーぽよ！わかるわけないっしょ！
I don't know-po! There's no way I'd know!
おいすこん部、どうなってんだよ。これだよ、これ。これ。
Hey Sukonbu, what's going on. This one, this one. This.
全部？全部おすすめ。ダメだ、IQどうなってんだよ。
All of them? All recommended. No good, what's with your IQ.
頑張ってフブさん。私のおすすめこれ。
Do your best, Fubusan. My recommendation is this.
真ん中？真ん中だって。えー、じゃあ。
The middle? She said the middle. Eh, then.
じゃあ真ん中おすすめされたから、真ん中いくか。
真ん中、すいちゃんのおすすめを信じて。
Since the middle was recommended, I'll go for it.
The middle, trusting Suichan's recommendation.
さあどうだ、すいちゃんのおすすめを信じる。移動されました。
Now then, I'll trust Suichan's recommendation. They were moved.
では、揃っているんですか？オープン！
Now then, did they match? Open!
は！揃ってる！揃ってる！
Ha! It matched! It matched!
揃ったということで、もう一回引くことができます。
Since you matched, you can pull one more time.
どっちだ、どっちだ、どっちなんだ！
Which one is it? Which one is it? Which one!?
えー、どうしよう。
Eh, what should I do?
さあどっちにするんですか？
Now, which one will it be?
どうしようか。
What should I do?
えー、これもういいのかい？
Eh, is this really okay?
どっちかでいいよ。
Either one is fine.
え、すいちゃん...じゃあ...
Eh, Sui-chan... Well then...
詰めはどっちへ...私のおすすめ？
Which way for the finish... My recommendation?
みこちゃんのすすめ？
Miko-chan's recommendation?
どっち？
Which one?
こっちじゃ、こっち。
This one, this one.
えー、どう？
Eh, how about this?
え、みこちゃんの顔見てみ、笑ってる笑ってる。
Eh, look at Miko-chan's face, she's smiling, she's smiling!
え、みこちゃんの顔見てみ、どっちが正解かじゃ。
Eh, look at Miko-chan's face, trying to see which is correct.
うーん、どうかな、どっちが正解か。
Hmm, I wonder which one is right.
え、どっち？じゃあこっちかな。
Eh, which one? Then maybe this one.
どっち、じゃあこっちかな...
Which one, then maybe this one...
や、と見せかけてこっち！
No, actually, I'll go with this one!
どっちだ！こっちだ！きっと、白上のカードだ！
Which one! This one! I'm sure it's Shirakami's card!
ファイナルアンサーでいいのだな？
Is that your final answer?
ファイナルアンサー！
Final answer!
さあ、そのカードは！
Now, that card is!
オープン！
Open!
フブキング！
FBKINGDOM!
やったー！勝利！
Yay! Victory!
まさか...
No way...
やったー！勝ったー！
Yay! I won!
この私が負けるだなんて...
To think that I would lose...
お前ザコだな！
You're a weakling!
うう、ばかー！ばかー！
Uu, stupid! Stupid!
うー、やめてください。
Ugh, please stop.
ということで、この試合というかこのゲームは白上の勝ち！
And so, this match, or rather this game, is Shirakami's win!
まあ、そういうことにはなりますね。
Well, I guess it turns out that way.
勝者、フブさん！
The winner, Fubu-san!
え、やったよ！
Eh, I did it!
これでスコーンブ！
With this, Sukonbu!
これで我々も元に戻してもらえるよ、勝ったからね！
Now they'll have to turn us back, because we won!
しょうがないね、ゲームはここまでということで。
I guess we have no choice, since the game is over.
勝った勝った！
We won, we won!
じゃあ、しょうがないからね。
Well then, I guess we'll do it.
元に戻してあげますか。
Shall we turn them back?
うん、じゃあ、戻して戻して。
Yeah, well then, turn back, turn back.
え、みこさんが戻すんだよ。
Eh, Miko-san, you're the one turning them back.
戻して、え、どっち？
Turn back, eh, which one?
早く戻して！
Hurry and turn us back!
みこさんは賭け目はするけど、解きはできないよ。
Miko-san can cast spells, but she can't break them.
え、すいちゃんもかけることしかできないよ。
Eh, Sui-chan can only cast them too.
おい、揃いも揃ってポンコツかよ！
Hey, are both of you completely useless!?
何だよ！呪い解除の呪文とか学べよ！どうなってんだ！
What the heck! Learn a counter-curse spell! What's wrong with you!
だってもう、マナが...マナがないんだよ。
Because we're out of... we're out of mana.
マナがないよー。
There's no mana left.
何だよ！
What!?
とりあえず、やるだけやってみよう。
For now, let's at least try our best.
ほら、ここ魔法陣に立って立って。
Look, stand here on the magic circle.
やるだけやる、やるだけやる！
Just try it! Just try it!
よし。
Alright.
ビビデバビデブー！
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo!
あ、ダメだ。
Ah, it's no good.
ダメじゃん。
It failed.
ということでね、魔力が足りないんで。
So, because we're lacking magical power...
どういうこと！？
What does that mean!?
ちょっとみこちゃんたちはお疲れモードなので、ここで帰らせていただきます。
Miko-chan and the others are in tired mode, so we're heading home now.
おいおい！
Hey, hey!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
ちょっと待って！このままってこと！？
Wait a minute! You mean we're staying like this!?
帰るよー。
We're leaving.
ガチで帰るよー。
We're seriously leaving.
行くぜ！バイバイ！
Let's go! Bye-bye!
待って待って、やめてやめて！
Wait, wait! Stop, stop!
転けた！この小さい体になれてないよ、痛いよ！
I tripped! I'm not used to this small body yet, it hurts!
マジで帰っちゃったんですけど、あの二人。
They seriously left, those two.
どうしよう...
What should I do...
どうしよう、スコーンブ、我々このまんまだよ。
What should I do, Sukonbu? We're stuck like this.
これからこの姿で配信しなきゃいけないってこと？
Does this mean we have to stream in this form from now on?
ホロライブのマスコットになるってこと？
Does it mean we're becoming Hololive mascots?
フブラも困惑しておる。
Fubra is also confused.
え、なんか、どうしよう、どうしたらいいんだろう...
Eh, what should I do? What can I do...
何？何？フブキスコーンブ。
What is it? What, Fubuki Sukonbu?
歌ってこと？なんかライブ？
Singing? Some kind of live performance?
あ、このまま歌い続ければもしかすると歌の力で元に戻るかもしれない！
Ah, if we keep singing like this, maybe the power of song will turn us back!
確かにこのお城も歌の皆の力で建ったしね。
It's true that this castle was built with the power of everyone's songs too.
フブラもそう思うか。
Do you think so too, Fubra?
ほんまか。
For real?
じゃあちょっとこのまま我々三人で歌い踊り...
Then, let's keep singing and dancing, the three of us...
その力でこの呪いを解くぞ！
And with that power, let's break this curse!
おー！！
Oh!!
よし、準備だ！
Alright, let's get ready!
Everything’s gonna be alright　感じよう今　噂の Be with you
Everything's gonna be alright. Let's feel it now, the rumored Be with you.
KONKON Beats / 作詞・作曲・編曲：TOKO TOKO
KONKON Beats / Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: TOKO TOKO
沈む太陽におはようと言ってみたり　真昼の月におやすみと言ってみたり
Saying good morning to the setting sun, or saying good night to the midday moon.
いつだって僕らはちょっとズレている　丸い地球のせいかもね
We're always a little bit off, maybe it's the round earth's fault.
下を向きたい時だってキツネ魂　そこんとこよろしくね
Even when I want to look down, I've got my fox spirit, so keep that in mind.
世界中が相手って無理じゃないってことも　今さらホントになる
The fact that taking on the whole world isn't impossible is finally becoming real.
Are you ready?　コン・コン・コン！
Are you ready? Kon Kon Kon!
よしそんなキツネに化かされて
Alright, get tricked by a fox like that.
Knock Knock Knock!　心を開けて
Knock Knock Knock! Open your heart.
Everything’s gonna be alright
Everything's gonna be alright.
感じよう今
Let's feel it now.
噂の Be with you
The rumored Be with you.
ヘイ　嫌なことがあった日でも
笑えちゃう僕らがいいね
Hey, even on days when bad things happen,
it's nice that we can laugh.
そうだ君のせいとならば　ケーキじゃないってことよ
今でも本気にする
That's right, if it's because of you, it's not a piece
of cake; I still take it seriously.
生まれも育ちも離す言葉も
趣味も歩幅も人の愛し方も
Birthplace, upbringing, the language we speak,
hobbies, stride, and how we love...
いつだって僕らはちょっとズレている
それを大事にしてよ
We're always a little out of sync;
please cherish that.
アイ・ビー・コンコン・コン！
イエスそんな狐に化かされて
ノック・ノック・ノック！　心を開けて
I be Kon-Kon-Kon!
Yes, bewitched by such a fox.
Knock, knock, knock! Open your heart.
オーイェー　エブリシング　ゴナ・ビー・オールライトな感じを
今うわずら　Feeling with you
Oh yeah, everything's gonna be alright.
Right now, right here, feeling with you.
もう一回コンコン・コン！
イエスそんな狐に化かされて
ノック・ノック・ノック！　心を開けて
Once more, Kon-Kon-Kon!
Yes, bewitched by such a fox.
Knock, knock, knock! Open your heart.
ウー・イェー・ダンス・ザ・ミュージック
ほら朝まで行くよ　今地球の裏にチューニング
Woo yeah, dance the music!
Look, we're going until morning.
Tuning to the other side of the Earth.
ウォー・コンコン・コン！　魔法をかけて
ウー・ベイベー　夜が明けるまで
Feeling with you
Woah, Kon-Kon-Kon! Cast a spell.
Ooh baby, until the dawn, feeling with you.
はぁ〜、コンコンビーツ楽しかったけど、
この体大変だよ〜！
Phew, KONKON Beats was fun,
but this body is hard work!
いやでも、すこん部なかなかやるやんけ。
白上の体を使いこなしておる。
But wow, Sukonbu, you're doing a great job.
You're mastering Shirakami's body.
でも、やっぱね、この体が恋しいよね？
But, you know, you miss this body, don't you?
おー！やっぱりそうだよね！
すこん部はこの体じゃなきゃね！
Oh! You're right!
Sukonbu has to be in this body!
でもまぁ白上もね、こんな経験なかなかないからさ、
最後にちょっと記念撮影しようや。ねっ！
But well, I don't get many chances for an experience
like this, so let's take a photo at the end. Okay?
よし！じゃあちょっと持ち上げてもらおうかな。
持ち上げてくれ。よいしょ。よいしょ。
Alright! Then, maybe you can lift me up.
Lift me. Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
おぉ〜！浮いた！お写真撮って〜！
Whoa! I'm floating! Take a picture!
わ〜い！イェ〜イ！
Yay! Yay!
よいしょ、ありがとう。下ろしてくれ。よいしょ〜。
There we go, thanks. Put me down. Heave-ho.
じゃあそろそろね、元の体にお互い戻りましょう。
よいしょ。
Well then, it's about time we both return to our
original bodies. Here we go.
多分ね、この辺に来れば魔法陣が出てくるはずだから。
I think if we come around here, the magic circle
should appear.
では行きますよ。出でよ！魔法陣！！
Here we go. Appear! Magic Circle!!
うわ〜！来た〜！戻れるのか〜！？
Whoa! It's here! Are we going back!?
あ！戻れた〜！やった〜！よかったよかった。
すこん部もちゃんとすこん部。
Ah! I'm back! I did it! Thank goodness.
Sukonbu is properly Sukonbu again.
あ〜！すこん部〜！やっぱその体が一番いいよね。
ね、ありがとう。
Ah! Sukonbu! That body really is the best for you.
Right? Thank you.
よし！じゃあすこん部、このまま一緒に歌いたいけども、
次の曲はちょっと白上頑張るから、またね、あの、
ステージの前で応援しててくれい！
Alright! Well Sukonbu, I'd love to keep singing
together, but I'm going to give it my all for the next
song, so cheer for me from the front of the stage!
気を付けて！
Take care!
かわいい。かわいい。もう去り方がかわいいね、
すこん部〜。
Cute. So cute. Even the way you leave is cute,
Sukonbu.
え〜、見てくれてるすこん部のみんなも、かわいいぞ！
And all the Sukonbu fans watching are cute too!
では、では、では、まだまだ応援してくれますよね？
ね？ありがとう！
Now, now, now, you're still going to cheer for me,
right? Right? Thank you!
よし！では、次の曲いきましょう。
次の曲は、「LETTER」。
Alright! Then, let's move on to the next song.
The next song is "LETTER".
Dear My Friend　ありがとうを込めて
君の名はかけがえのない光
Dear My Friend, with all my thanks,
your name is an irreplaceable light.
見上げたって　頑張れるんだって
言葉ひとつで願いは叶う　限界と呼ばれたって
生きる理由なんです
Even if I look up, I can do my best.
Wishes come true with one word. Even if they call it
my limit, it's my reason for living.
へこたれたって　見失ったって
また私を照らしてくれる　心臓は鷲掴みされて
気絶しちゃいそうです
Even if I feel down or lose my way,
you'll light my path again. My heart is being gripped
so tight, I feel like I might faint.
一生懸命な姿に何度も勇気もらったから
今度は私がエールになりたい
I've been given courage so many times by your hard-
working self, so this time I want to be your support.
歌え全熱量の賛歌
Sing a hymn of total passion.
Dear My Friend　大好きがあふれた
この想いお手紙に書いて送ります
Dear My Friend, overflowing with love,
I'll write these feelings in a letter and send them.
You Make My Day　夢を叶えて
君の笑顔が私のエネルギー
You Make My Day, granting my dreams,
your smile is my energy.
You'll always be the first in my heart
どこまでもついて…
You'll always be the first in my heart,
follow me anywhere...
Let you go, I follow you forever
幸せって 君と出会って
Happiness is meeting you,
過ごす日々だと定義された
and it was defined by the days we spend.
会えない時間だっていい
The time we can't meet is fine too.
愛を育てろって事です
It just means to nurture our love.
どうしたって 叫びたくなる
No matter what, I want to scream.
イタズラが功を奏したのかも
Maybe the prank worked out.
来世も来来来世までも語り継ぎたいのです
I want to tell our story even to the next life.
一瞬一瞬がときめく 両手にいっぱいの思い出
Every single moment thrills me, both hands full of memories.
確かめ合えば寂しくないから つなげて絆の結晶
If we confirm it together, we won't be lonely, let's connect the crystal of our bond.
Be my faith! 頑張ってなんて言えない
Be my faith! I can't just say "Good luck!"
「大丈夫」の三文字で伝わるかな
I wonder if I can convey it with the words "It's okay."
Day by day さあ 君のおかげで
Day by day, now, thanks to you.
少しだけ自分を好きになれたから
I've come to like myself just a little bit more.
君らしく keep smiling enjoy yourself
Just be yourself, keep smiling and enjoy yourself.
心から願うわ 私がいる 一人じゃない
I wish from the bottom of my heart, I'm here, you're not alone.
Be my faith! 大好きを集めた
Be my faith! I've gathered all my favorites.
合言葉 手紙に書いて送るね
I'll write the password in a letter and send it to you.
You make my days 夢で終わらない
You make my days, it's not just a dream.
君だけが 君こそが起こす奇跡
Only you, it's you who makes the miracle happen.
You will always be the fan in my heart
信じてよ 夜空の星のようにずっと
Please believe me, forever like the stars in the night sky.
I will follow you forever
ありったけの愛を込めて ありがとう
With all the love I have, thank you.
君と歩むたった一つの奇跡
The one and only miracle of walking with you.
銀河を超えて風合わせ 輝かせて
Crossing the galaxy, meeting the wind, make it shine.
Best wishes to you la la la la...
はい！ということで、LETTER☆彡！
Yes! So that was LETTER☆彡!
みんなコメントもいっぱい！ありがとう！
So many comments everyone! Thank you!
ちょっと、しんどいですね...
I'm a bit out of breath...
はい！いやもう本当に、やっぱりLETTERは楽しいですね。
Yes! Wow, LETTER is really fun after all.
そしてこの身体がやっぱりしっくりくるんだ！
And this body really feels right after all!
ふぅ〜。みんな、いっぱい盛り上がってくれてありがとうございます！
Phew. Thank you everyone for getting so excited!
さてさて、ではもうね、いいお時間なので、
Now then, since it's about that time,
重大告知、えー、1個目、
The first, uh, major announcement,
発表したいと思いまーす！
I'd like to announce it!
なんと、なんと、なんと...
Guess what, guess what, guess what...
新曲がありまーす！
There's a new song!
わー！
Yay!
新曲だ！
A new song!
嬉しい新曲だ！
I'm so happy, it's a new song!
あれ？待って？あれ？
Wait? What? Huh?
もしかして、その声は...あれ？
Could it be, those voices are...?
およ〜？
Oyo~?
すいちゃん？
Suichan?
あれ？みこさん？
Wait, Miko-san?
すこん部だよ。
They're Sukombu.
え、待って、どっち、え、スカーフの方がこっち？
Wait, which one... is the scarf one this one?
こっちが...
Is this one...
すいちゃーん！
Suichan!
すいちゃん！
すいちゃん、スコン部になっちゃったの！？
Suichan, you became a Sukombu!?
すこんぶ、すこんぶ〜！
Sukombu, sukombu!
わ〜！
Wow!
小さくなっちゃって。
You've become so small.
わ〜、しっぽもふもふ。で、こっち子...
Wow, the tail is so fluffy. And this one...
みこ〜！
Miko!
みこだぉ〜！
It's Miko!
みこさん。
Miko-san.
あれ？みこさん、そのリボンはね、
Oh? Miko-san, that ribbon is,
あの、海外すこん部、いわゆるフレ（フレンド）ズなんだけど、
uh, Overseas Sukombu, the so-called "Friends."
みこさん、あれ、もしや海外...
Miko-san, could it be you're Overseas...
え？よく、もしやENのスコン部ってこと？
Eh? So does that mean I'm an EN Sukombu?
ハイフレ。ハイフレ。
Hi-fre! Hi-fre!
なっちゃったんだ。お、え〜、
You became one. Oh, uh...
すこんぶだよ。
It's a Sukombu.
すいちゃんもこれJPのすこんぶになっちゃって。
Suichan has become a JP Sukombu too.
あらら。
Oh dear.
二人とも、あれ、どうしたの？
What happened to you two?
なんかさっき本当アホみたいな呪いをかけて...
Like you put some really stupid curse on earlier...
アホじゃないよ！アホじゃないよ！
It's not stupid! It's not stupid!
さっきフブさんが元の姿に戻ったでしょ？
Fubu-san went back to her original form earlier, right?
そしたらこんな風になっちゃった。
Then we ended up like this.
逆に？
The other way around?
あの呪いが返ってきたんだ。かわいそう。
The curse came back. Poor things.
アホ呪い二人だから。
Because you're the "Stupid Curse Duo."
悪いことするから。
Because you did something bad.
お前のせいだろ！お前が悪いんだよ！
It's your fault! You're the one to blame!
お前のせいだ！
It's your fault!
あーっ！ちょっと、何やって、これ。
Ah! Hey, what are you doing?
戦うな戦うな。これから歌うんだよ。
Don't fight, don't fight. We're going to sing now.
やめなさい。
Stop it.
今からわが新曲発表するって
I heard you're announcing a new song now.
あ、そうだよ
Ah, that's right.
新曲なんですか？
Is it a new song?
そうなんですよ、なんとですね...
That's right, and guess what...
みんなコメントも可愛いって
Everyone is saying it's cute in the comments.
可愛いって言ってるよ
They're saying we're cute.
当たり前じゃん
Of course we are.
俺ら可愛い
We're cute.
当たり前じゃん
Of course we are.
当たり前じゃん、俺ら可愛い
Of course we are, we're cute.
これが新しいフブニコメントさんの姿だよ
This is the new look of Fubunicomet-san.
嘘でしょ、嘘でしょ
No way, no way.
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
そんなので呪い解いてあげる
I'll break the curse for you.
同じ顔しないで、差別できなくなる
Don't make the same face, I won't be able to tell you apart.
差別、区別ね
Distinction, you mean.
うわぁ、じゃあないんだよ
Whoa, it's not "whoa".
えっと、ごめんごめん、えっと、今から新曲...
Um, sorry, sorry, um, now the new song...
アルバムからですね、作詞・作曲・編曲 Revoさんの楽曲を...
From the album, a song with lyrics, composition, and arrangement by Revo...
...歌わせていただこうと思います！
...I'm going to sing!
えー、すごい！
Whoa, amazing!
Revo、総力戦すぎるでしょ
Revo, that's such an all-out effort.
でもね、わかるわかる、わかるわかる
But you know, I get it, I get it.
あー、すっちゃん分かりそうだけどね
Ah, Su-chan seems to get it.
すっちゃん分かってない、分かるよ
Su-chan doesn't get it. I do!
心臓を捧げるんだよ
Dedicating your heart.
そうだね、そういう曲作ってる方ですね
Right, he's the one who makes those kinds of songs.
ちなみに21時30分からですね、こちらの「僕らの星座」という楽曲...
By the way, from 21:30, the music video for this song "Bokura no Seiza"...
...MV公開予定でございますので、そちらもよろしくお願いしまーす！
...is scheduled to be released, so please check that out too!
絶対買ってね、絶対よろしく
Be sure to buy it, please.
買えよ、聴けよ、21時から配信もございます、聴いてね
Buy it, listen to it, there's also a stream from 21:00, listen to it.
おい、おい！
Oi, oi!
ということで、今から歌わせていただくんですけども...
So, I'm going to sing now...
え、フブニコメントもしかしていてくれるの？
Wait, Fubunicomet, are you going to stay?
フブちゃん、フブちゃん
Fubu-chan, Fubu-chan.
ニコメットはずっと一緒だよ、嘘だよ
Nicomets are always together. Just kidding.
いつでも一緒だよ
Always together.
そうなの、じゃあ、一緒にちょっとパフォーマンスしてくれるの？
Is that so? Then, will you perform with me for a bit?
当たり前じゃん！
Of course!
やったー！
Yay!
じゃあ、この「僕らの星座」、前に円形ステージがあるので...
Well then, for "Bokura no Seiza", there's a circular stage in front...
...そこで一緒に踊りましょう、歌って踊りましょう
...so let's dance together there, let's sing and dance.
わかった、はい
Got it, yes.
それでは聴いてください、「僕らの星座」、ゴー！
Then please listen, "Bokura no Seiza", go!
僕らの星座
作詞・作曲・編曲：Revo
Bokura no Seiza
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Revo
始まりはきっと一つの願い
It surely started with a single wish
それを抱いて私は生まれた
Embracing it, I was born
孤独な夜空震える指で
In the lonely night sky, with trembling fingers
点と点を繋げよう
Let's connect the dots
1次元では寂しすぎるから
Because it's too lonely in one dimension
私たちは広がりを求めた
We sought to expand
点は線となり線は立体となり
Dots became lines, lines became solids
そこに距離が生まれたけれど
And though distance was born there
3次元ではちょっと遠すぎるから
Because it's a bit too far in three dimensions
私たちは平面に求めた
We sought it on a plane
点は星となり星は星座となり
Dots became stars, stars became constellations
この夜空を繋ぐよ
Connecting this night sky
自分らしくいられる場所を
A place where I can be myself
気付けばずっと探していた
I realized I'd been searching for it all along
煌めく星を飾り留め
Gathering and fixing the sparkling stars
この白旗を目印に
Using this white flag as a marker
あの日君がいつもそこにいたから
Because you were always there that day
嬉しくて続けられたんだ今日まで
I was so happy I could keep going until today
忘れないでね僕らの星座は
Please don't forget, our constellation
君がいたから生まれた
Was born because you were here
2次元では楽しすぎたから
Because it was too much fun in two dimensions
私たちは毎日を笑った
We laughed every day
秒は分となり分は時間となり
Seconds became minutes, minutes became hours
辛いことも忘れて
Forgetting even the painful things
自分らしく笑える場所を
A place where I can laugh like myself
気付けば闇に星は満ちた
I realized the darkness was filled with stars
重ねる歌で思いを刻め
Carve your thoughts with layered songs
この白亜の城壁に
On these white castle walls
だから君がいつか自分自身の輝きを見失ったときには
So when you one day lose sight of your own brilliance
思い出してね僕らの星座は
Please remember, our constellation
君がいるから輝く
Shines because you are here
Woh oh...
たとえ幾千の
Even if thousands of
時を生きても
years pass,
何かを好きになる気持ち
the feeling of liking something,
大切に歌い続けてね
please keep singing while cherishing it.
僕らの星座は
Our constellation
君がいるから生まれたよ
was born because you are here.
空に輝き
Shining in the sky,
明日へとつながる
connecting to tomorrow.
Woh oh...
未来を
To the future,
目指すよ
we'll aim.
共にゆこう
Let's go together.
こうして一夜の音楽祭が終わり、
And so, the one-night music festival ended,
国民たちは笑顔で帰宅をするのでした。
and the citizens returned home with smiles.
しかし、ふと寂しい気持ちにもなります。
However, they suddenly felt a bit lonely.
画面越しの世界、
The world beyond the screen,
現実に。
to reality.
始まりはきっと　一つの願い
The beginning is surely a single wish.
それを抱いて私たちは
Holding onto it, we
生まれた孤独な夜空
were born into the lonely night sky.
震える指で
With trembling fingers,
点と点を繋げよう
let's connect the dots.
Woh oh...
フブキングダム 王国をあげてのお祭りを君と一緒に創りたい
FBKINGDOM: I want to create a kingdom-wide festival together with you.
白上フブキ 1stソロライブ 開催決定
Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live Announcement
はい！ということで！
Yes! So!
もうみんなわかってたと思いますけども！
I think everyone already knew, but!
白上フブキ初のソロライブ開催決定しましたー！
Shirakami Fubuki's first solo live has been announced!
もうさー、みんなにしつこいくらい言われた
Man, I was asked so many times
「ソロライブやるんですか？」って
about whether I was doing a solo live,
その度に否定しなきゃいけない日々。
and I had to deny it every time.
大変、苦痛でございました。
It was very painful.
否定してましたね。
You were denying it.
その度に否定しまくって、ないのかって
By denying it every time,
寂しい思いをさせてしまったすこんぶごめんなさい。
I'm sorry to the Sukonbu for making you feel lonely.
やります！
I'm doing it!
やったー！
Yay!
はい！ということで開催日程は、
Yes! So the dates are
2025年2月13日で、
February 13, 2025,
会場は横浜のぴあアリーナMMで開催します！
and the venue will be Pia Arena MM in Yokohama!
まじか。
Seriously.
てか、てか二人さ、そのままでいいの？
By the way, are you two okay like that?
戻る？戻れるよ多分。
Going back? You probably can.
ああ、大丈夫。
Ah, it's fine.
楽しかった。
It was fun.
すこんぶだもんね。
We're Sukonbu after all.
二人がさ、踊ったから戻れるけど。
You two danced, so you can go back.
二人がさ、歌ってたらさ、
If you two were singing,
前でガッチャンコしそうになったから戻って。
you looked like you were going to collide in front, so go back.
必死にさ、笑わないように歌ってる間邪魔にならないようにさ。
I was desperately trying not to laugh so I wouldn't get in the way while you were singing.
ごめんね、無言でさ、お互いアイコンタクト取りながらさ。
Sorry, we were making eye contact silently.
もうダメだ、笑いが止まらん。
I can't stop laughing.
3周、白上の周りをくるくる回ってさ。
Circling around me three times.
だってこんなにファンシーなすいちゃん初めて見たよ。
I've never seen such a fancy Sui-chan before.
こんなファンシーなみこち初めて見たよ。
I've never seen such a fancy Mikochi before.
可愛い。
So cute.
可愛い。もうすこんぶも喜んでます。
Cute. The Sukonbu are happy too.
喜んでる。本当におめでとう。
They're happy. Congratulations.
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
きました新曲「僕らの星座」はですね
Our new song "Our Constellation" is...
このライブに向けて制作しました
...produced specifically for this live event.
フブキングダムの国歌でございます！
It is the national anthem of Fubukingdom!
おおー！
Ooh!
あ、あの、ソロライブでは多分、多分、いやきっとメイビー、もちろん歌います！
Um, at the solo live, I'll probably, definitely, maybe, of course I'll sing it!
なので、みんなにはこの曲覚えてほしい！
So, I want everyone to learn this song!
おー！
Oh!
ワーアーオー、ワーアーオー...
Wa-a-o, wa-a-o...
そ、そこもなんだけど、よかったらもう1番から、もう頭から...
T-That part too, but if you could, from the first verse, from the very beginning...
お尻ケツまで、うわっとみんなで大合唱したいんですよ、会場で！
...to the very end, I want to have a massive sing-along at the venue!
おおー！
Ooh!
なので、ちょっとこの曲ぜひ覚えて会場のみんなで歌いましょう！
So, please learn this song and let's sing it together at the venue!
よろしくお願いします！
I look forward to it!
覚える！
We'll learn it!
覚えてください！
Please learn it!
MVがこの後21時30分、そして24時からは楽曲配信もございますので
The MV will be out at 21:30, and from 24:00 the song will be on streaming services,
アルバムの中には入ってる曲なんですけど、先に覚えていただけると嬉しいです！
it's on the album, but I'd be happy if you learned it beforehand!
おぼえるー！
We'll learn it!
はい、ではちょっとライブ情報に戻りまして
Okay, returning to the live information...
続いてはですね、ライブのキービジュアル公開します！
...next, I'm revealing the key visual for the live!
こちら！
Here it is!
ドン！
Ta-da!
おおー！
Ooh!
はい！もうね、めちゃめちゃカッコカワいい、しらかみを描いていただきました！
Yes! I had an incredibly cool and cute Shirakami drawn!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
神々しいよ！
So divine!
王者だ！
A ruler!
王様だ！
A king!
王様で...
As a king...
マスコットの皆のも、あれ？
...and the mascots for everyone too, huh?
ミコメットですか、あれは？
Is that Mikomet?
あれってミコメット？
あ、すいちゃんなの？
Oh, is that Sui-chan?
ちがいます、コン部員です！
No, they are the Kon-bu members!
嘘でしょ？
No way?
コン部員のみんなです！
They are all Kon-bu members!
公演ハッシュタグは、#DearFBKINGDOM でどんどんポストして盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you post with the hashtag #DearFBKINGDOM and hype it up!
お願いします！
Please!
さらに、トリミング前のイラストも公開しちゃいます！こちら！
Furthermore, I'm revealing the full illustration before cropping! Here!
デーン！
Ta-da!
きれいな足がね！
Look at those beautiful legs!
そう！
Right!
足長い！
Long legs!
実はですね、もうすごーい足長アングルで描いていただきました！
Actually, it was drawn from a very leg-lengthening angle!
素晴らしいです！もうホクホクの金だね！
It's wonderful! It's like warm gold!
そう、金も舞って、こう紙吹雪も舞ってます！
Yes, gold is dancing, and confetti is also dancing!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
続いてはですね、チケット情報いきましょうか！
Next, let's move on to the ticket information!
こちらをご覧ください！
Please take a look at this!
はい、チケットはS席、A席、B席の3種類です！
Yes, there are three types of tickets: S, A, and B seats!
さらに、海外コン部員向けにも ZAIKO で現地チケットを販売いたします！
Furthermore, venue tickets will be on sale at ZAIKO for overseas fans!
やったー！
Yay!
Hi Friends! We will sell the venue ticket for you. It will be on sale after the stream, so please get ready!
イェーイ！
Yay!
届いてくれたかな？海外の兄貴もぜひ来てください！
Did that reach you? Overseas brothers, please come by all means!
現地チケットの1次先行がなんとこの後21時から開始となります！
First advance sales for venue tickets will start at 21:00!
ぜひチェックしてください！
Please check it out!
チケットは先着ではなく抽選方式なので、焦らずに申し込みをお願いします！
Tickets are by lottery, not first-come-first-served, so please apply without rushing!
次に配信チケット、みこさん達は吊るし席ですけど、我々コン部はですね、ダンボールという名の家がありますので、ダンボール席でございます！
Next, streaming tickets. Miko-san and others have hanging seats, but we fans have "cardboard box" seats!
ダンボール席？
Cardboard seats?
はい、配信チケット(ダンボール席)は SPWN と ZAIKO で販売いたします！
Yes, streaming tickets (cardboard seats) will be on sale at SPWN and ZAIKO!
こちらもこの後21時から販売開始なので、現地に来れないよという方はですね、
Sales for these also start at 21:00, so if you can't come to the venue,
配信のダンボールの中から白上を応援してくれると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you cheer for Shirakami from inside your cardboard streaming boxes!
お願いします！
Please!
続いて、各座席のエリアマップをご覧ください！どうぞ！
Next, please see the area map for each seat! Here!
デーン！
Ta-da!
おー！広い！ぴあアリーナってすごい広いんだよね！
Oh! So wide! Pia Arena is really spacious!
すごいよ！ぴあアリーナMMだよ！ちょっと今だに実感わかないんですけども、
It's amazing! It's Pia Arena MM! I still can't believe it's real, but...
1階のアリーナがS席！
The first floor arena is the S-seat!
2階と3階中央がA席！
The second floor and the center of the third floor are A-seats!
3階の一部と4階がB席ということで、4階まである！
Part of the third floor and the fourth floor are B-seats. There's even a fourth floor!
S、S当てたい！
I want to get an S-seat!
S当てたい！1階！
I want an S-seat! First floor!
え、すいちゃんも？みこさんも？
Eh, Sui-chan too? Miko-san too?
すいちゃんも！
Sui-chan too!
みこも！
Miko too!
え、関係者席用意するが...
Eh, I'll prepare guest seats...
え、嘘だよ！だめです！
Eh, just kidding! No!
来ちゃダメです！
You can't come!
二人もダンボール席かもしれないねー
Maybe you two will be in cardboard seats too.
おおー！
Ooh!
はい！じゃあチケットも出ましたので、続いては皆さんお待ちかねのグッズ情報です！こちら！
Okay! Now that the ticket info is out, next is the merch info you've all been waiting for! Here!
ドン！
Ta-da!
まずは、白上フブキ 1st ソロライブ「フブキングダム応援セット」をご紹介！
First, introducing the Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live "Fubukingdom Support Set"!
こちらですね、応援セットの「入国証明キーホルダー」以外、あ、Tシャツ以外は、
For this, except for the "Entry Certificate Keychain" and the T-shirt,
実はペンライト、すこん部タオル全部白上がデザインさせていただきました！
I actually designed the penlight and the Sukonbu towel myself!
おー！すごい！
Oh! Amazing!
はい！まずはですね、こちらのセットなんですけど、
Yes! First, about this set...
このセットを買うと、入国証明キーホルダー付いてきます！
...if you buy this set, it comes with the Entry Certificate Keychain!
国民ペンライトはですね、運営さんと一緒に「こんな感じにお願いします！」
For the citizen penlight, I told the staff, "Please make it like this!"
「この形でお願いします！」って白上がもう土下座して頼んだ結果、
I begged on my hands and knees saying "Please use this shape!"
作っていただいたペンライトでございます！
...and this is the result of their hard work!
今回のライブテーマの「フブキングダム」に相応しい王冠をあしらったデザインとなってまして、
The design features a crown befitting the live theme "Fubukingdom",
ライブ会場で国民の皆が振るライトにピッタリな仕上がりとなっております！
it's the perfect light for all the citizens to wave at the venue!
かっこいいね！
It looks cool!
そう！形はね、すこん部なんだけど、中に国章のマークが入っております！
Right! The shape is Sukonbu, but it has the national emblem inside!
かっこいい！
Cool!
ぜひぜひ振ってください！
Please wave it!
そしてTシャツはですね、今回の公演特別仕様...
And the T-shirt is a special version for this performance...
はい、です。
Yes, it is.
特にね背面に、
Especially on the back,
白上としっぽ...しっぽと言いますか、星マークと描き下ろしイラストが実は入ってるんです。
there's actually a tail... or rather, a star mark and a newly drawn illustration by me.
本当だ！
It's true!
はい。ここにTシャツの隅っこに「落書きしていいですか？」って言ったら
Yes. I asked, "Can I doodle in the corner of the T-shirt here?"
「いいよ」って言ってくれたので、白上がちょっと描かせていただきました。
and they said, "Sure," so I drew a little something.
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
はい。ぜひね、ライブといえばTシャツということで。皆さんにぜひ着てきてほしいなと思っております。
Yes. T-shirts are a must for live shows, so I really hope everyone wears one.
そして「すこん部タオル」は、フードを被るとみんなすこん部！
And the "Sukonbu Towel" makes everyone a Sukonbu when you put the hood on!
可愛ちいすこん部になれちゃいまーす。
You can become a cute Sukonbu!
ちょっとね、スカーフが確かないので。海外のね、すこん部は
It doesn't have the scarf, though. Overseas Sukonbu might think,
「あれ？リボンじゃないの？」なんですけども。よければこちらも着てきてくれると嬉しいです。
"Wait, shouldn't it be a ribbon?" but I'd be happy if you wore this too.
これね、スカーフのところがボタンで止めれるようになってますので、
The scarf part can be fastened with a button,
Tシャツの上からでも羽織ってこれます。よろしくお願いします。
so you can wear it over a T-shirt. Please check it out.
わー！
Wow!
はい。で、応援セット買ってくれた方には「入国証明キーホルダー」が特典で付いてきまーす。
Yes. And for those who buy the support set, an "Entry Certificate Keyholder" comes as a bonus.
これ、パスポートに押す入国スタンプをイメージした感じとなっております。
This is designed to look like an entry stamp you'd get in a passport.
で、これを付ければ、あなたも国民の仲間入り...なのかな？
And if you wear this, you'll be one of the citizens... maybe?
入国するー！入国させてよー！
I'm entering! Let me in!
はい。そしてグッズはまだまだございます。こちら、ドン！
Yes. And there's still more merchandise. Here they are, boom!
はい。「応援セット」はですね、単品でも販売させていただきます。
Yes. The items in the "Support Set" will also be sold individually.
別売りの「缶バッジ」とですね、FBKINGDOM腕章がなんとこちらにはございます。
We also have a "Can Badge" and an "FBKINGDOM Armband" sold separately.
缶バッジはですね、金木犀をあしらったゴージャスな缶バッジとなっております。
The can badge is a gorgeous one decorated with osmanthus flowers.
もうね、最近すこん部の皆さんがね、痛バ作ってくれたりとか。
Lately, many Sukonbu have been making "ita-bags".
夏に白上が「推し活グッズ」としてちょっとミコメットとお揃っちのあのカバンを出させていただきましたので。
Since I released those matching bags with Mikomet as "oshikatsu goods" in the summer.
ちょっと、そちらにもぜひ、この缶バッジで痛バ作っていただきたいなと思っております。
I'd love for you to use these can badges to make an ita-bag with those, too.
そして「FBKINGDOM 腕章」はですね、応援セットと合わせてちょっと国民の正装に必要なアイテムかなと思いました。
And the "FBKINGDOM Armband" is an item I thought would be necessary for the citizens' formal attire, combined with the support set.
ぜひね、腕に付けてきてほしいなと思っております。
I really hope you'll wear it on your arm.
なんかちょっと「正装感」、正装してきてる感がありますので。
It gives a sense of being "formally dressed," like you're dressed up for the occasion.
スーツで行くね！
I'll go in a suit!
スーツで来るの！？ちょっと動きにくいかもだけど、
You're coming in a suit!? It might be hard to move in,
でもスーツもかっこいいかもしれない。なんかそういう、ちょっとおしゃれな感じで来てくださると嬉しいです。
but a suit could be cool too. I'd be happy if you came looking a bit stylish like that.
えー、そしてですね。こちら缶バッジとFBKINGDOM腕章は単品のみの販売となっておりますので。
Also, the can badge and the FBKINGDOM armband are sold individually only.
先ほど紹介した応援セットには含まれませんので、そちらご注意ください。お願いします。
Please note that they are not included in the support set I introduced earlier. Thank you.
さらにさらにございます。受注生産グッズ、こちらです、どうぞ！ジャーン！
And there's even more. Made-to-order items are right here! Ta-da!
えー、こちらですね。「アクリルジオラマスタンド」は白上とすこん部たちでFBKINGDOMの世界観を再現することができます。
Here they are. The "Acrylic Diorama Stand" lets you recreate the world of FBKINGDOM with me and the Sukonbus.
なんとこちら、好きな位置に差し替えも可能なので、
Surprisingly, you can swap things into any position you like,
「マスコットこの位置がいいな」とか自分だけのアクリルジオラマ作ってみてください。
so please make your own acrylic diorama, like "I want the mascot here."
そして「タペストリー」なんですけど、実はこれよく見ると、アクリルジオラマスタンドと違う点があるんですよ。
And regarding the "Tapestry," if you look closely, there's actually a difference from the acrylic diorama stand.
さあ、どこでしょうか？
Now, where is it?
どこー？
Where?
スカーフの色！
The color of the scarf!
ブブー、違います。
Bzzzt! Wrong.
お、手が！きつねさんになっている！
Oh, the hand! It's doing the fox sign!
おー！すごい巫女さん、正解！
Oh! Amazing, Miko, you're right!
なんとですね、タペストリーの白上は左手がきつねサインになってます。
On the tapestry, my left hand is actually making the fox sign.
本当だ！
It's true!
こちらね、アクリルジオラマスタンドとタペストリーで2種類のキービジュアル楽しめますので、ぜひどちらもおうちに置いてください。よろしくお願いします。
So you can enjoy two different key visuals with the acrylic diorama stand and the tapestry. I hope you'll keep both at home. Thank you.
そして「タオルハンカチ」はですね、FBKINGDOMの紋章、国章ですね、使用しておりましてクールなデザインとなっております。
And the "Towel Handkerchief" uses the FBKINGDOM emblem, the national crest, and has a cool design.
ライブ以外での普段使いもできるデザインかなと思っておりますので、いろんな場所で使ってほしいです。
I think the design is suitable for everyday use outside of live shows, so I'd like you to use it in various places.
はい。
Yes.
はい。で、最後に注意事項です。気をつけるんですよ。
Yes. And finally, some precautions. Pay attention.
販売期間はこのあと21時から11月25日の18時までとなっております。
The sales period is from 9:00 PM tonight until 6:00 PM on November 25th.
そしてさらに注意していただきたいのが、グッズの発送時期についてです。
And something else I want you to be careful about is the shipping timing of the goods.
「先行発送グッズ」はライブの前に届く予定ですが、
The "Early Shipping Goods" are scheduled to arrive before the live show, but
「受注販売」のグッズはライブの後にお届けでございます。
the "Made-to-order" goods will be delivered after the live show.
また、先行発送グッズと受注販売のグッズを一緒のカートに入れて購入することはできません！
Also, you cannot purchase early shipping goods and made-to-order goods in the same cart!
なので、あの別会計でお願いします。ね。
So, please make separate payments. Yes.
先行先に買ったあとに受注販売のグッズを購入していただけると嬉しいです。別会計忘れずに！
I'd appreciate it if you'd buy the early shipping ones first, then the made-to-order goods. Don't forget, separate payments!
詳しくは公式X、販売サイト、公式特設サイトをご確認ください。
For details, please check official X, the sales site, and the official special site.
あー！こら！お前ら！
Ah! Hey! You guys!
全く、隙あらばすぐそうやって争んだ、ミコメットは。
Jeez, you Mikomets start fighting whenever you get a chance.
あいつが悪い！
It's his fault!
あいつが悪いもん！
えー、どっちもどっち悪いだろ全く。すぐそうやってイチャイチャすんだから。
Jeez, you're both at fault. Always flirting like that.
あ、違うか、ビジネスかこれも。
Oh, wait, is this business too?
これもビジネスなんだ。えー、そしてそして、
This is business too. I see. And then, and then...
白上フブキ1stアルバム「FBKINGDOM "Blessing"」について追加情報がございます！
There is additional information about my 1st album, "FBKINGDOM 'Blessing'"!
どうぞー
Here you go!
本日、通常版の店舗特典の絵柄を初公開！
Today, we're revealing the designs for the standard edition store bonuses!
イェーイ！
Yay!
店舗別の特典ですね。
These are bonuses for each store.
素敵な特典が盛りだくさんなので是非チェックしてください！
There are lots of great bonuses, so please check them out!
さらに！
Furthermore!
デデン！
Ta-da!
大好評いただき既に予約は終了してるんですけども、
Although reservations have already ended due to great popularity,
数量限定版の外箱のデザインがこちら、
the design for the limited edition outer box is this,
こちら、こちら、こちらです！
this, this, this, this!
ワーオ！
Wow!
あーやー、こちらもね、ちょっといい感じにお洒落な感じにしていただきました。
Ah, this one too, they made it look quite nice and stylish.
そして、さらにこちら！
And then, even more!
デューン！
Dun!
表情差分イラストを使用した
The album jacket design using an
アルバムのジャケットデザインが到着しました。
illustration with a different expression has arrived.
笑顔ー！
A smile!
可愛い
So cute!
はい、皆様こちら、アルバムご購入本当にありがとうございました。
Yes, everyone, thank you so much for purchasing the album.
通常版もございます。よろしくお願いします。
There's also a standard edition. Please check it out.
こちら届くの楽しみにしててください！
Please look forward to it arriving!
待ってね！
Wait for it!
ありがとうございまーす
Thank you very much!
そして最後に、本日よりこちら。
And finally, starting today...
おー、国王への忠誠を叫ぼう！
Oh, "Shout your loyalty to the King!"
ハッシュタグキャンペーンを実施します！
hashtag campaign!
ハッシュタグ「フブキングダムに納税」のハッシュタグをつけて
Use the hashtag "#TaxToFubukingdom"
SNSでとにかくフブキングダムを布教してくれい！
and spread the word about Fubukingdom on SNS!
これ納税とありますけども、まぁいつものね、
It says "tax", but please post anything,
応援コメントですとか、ファンアート、動画投稿など、
like your usual supportive comments, fan art, video posts, etc.,
何でもこちらハッシュタグ「フブキングダムに納税」をつけて
with the hashtag "#TaxToFubukingdom"!
投稿お願いします！
Please send in your posts!
納税！
Tax!
配信とかでちょっと、あの白上が、
I might introduce some posts
あ、これいいかもって思ったやつには、
that I think are good
ちょっと紹介させていただくこともあるかも...
during my streams...
えー！
Eh?!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Please look forward to it!
納税！
Tax!
ありがとう！これ是非とも投稿してくださーい！
Thank you! Please do post!
はい！ということで。
Alright! So...
さぁ全ての告知が終わっちゃいまして。
Now all the announcements are over.
ついにソロライブ告知しちゃった。
I finally announced my solo live.
おめでとー！
Congratulations!
やっと走り切る、抜け出せたね、お疲れ様！
You finally made it through! Good job!
そうだ、そうだ。
Right, right.
ありがと、ありがと。
Thank you, thank you.
なんか、すいちゃんの背中を見て、みこさんの背中も見、
Watching Suisei-chan's back, and Miko-san's back...
あ、すいちゃんはまだこれからだね。
Ah, Suisei-chan is still to come.
これからだね。
Still to come.
みこさんの背中を見送った後に、またすいちゃんがあって、
After seeing Miko-san off, there's Suisei-chan again,
それを追いかける形で、って、
and I'm following in their footsteps...
ちょっとね、フブキングダムさんでこうやって、
I'm glad I could make these
なんか色々ライブの発表ができたら嬉しかったなと思います。
live announcements through Fubukingdom.
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
はい、そしてもう21時なので、
Yes, and since it's already 9 PM,
多分そろそろあの、販売とかね、
sales should have started by now,
開始してるかと思いますのでよろしくお願いします。
so please check them out.
ということで、じゃあ本日は以上です！
So, that's all for today!
はい、二人とも最後に本当に元に戻らなくて大丈夫？
Okay, are you two really okay not turning back at the end?
あーん。
Um...
じゃあ最後は、じゃあね、これでバイバイして終わろうと思いまーす！
Well then, at the end, let's finish with a goodbye like this!
いきますよ、せーの！
Here we go, ready, set...
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!